Contact

bbynumiu14@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/britney-bynum-324575a0 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation (CPR)

Public Speaking Healthcare

Britney Bynum

Director of Nursing at Nurse

Munster, Indiana

Summary

I have been an asset to the medical field for 10 years. I love being a RN and I have enjoyed meeting new people, patients, and family members along the way. I am always excited to educate and train new staff. Most of all I make my career fun and keep the people around me laughing and smiling.

Experience

Nurse

Director of Nursing September 2019 - Present (11 months)

Great Lakes Healthcare Center
Director of Nursing
March 2017 - September 2019 (2 years 7 months)
Dyer, Indiana

Kindred

Staff Development Coordinator November 2015 - March 2017 (1 year 5 months) Indiana

Promote growth, develop, and train staff
Interview new candidates
Orientation
Infection Control Nurse

Workers Compensation

Acute Rehab Community Hospital May 2015 - June 2016 (1 year 2 months) Indiana

Golden Living Center Charge Nurse August 2014 - October 2015 (1 year 3 months) Indiana

Methodist Hospital Med-Surg RN December 2014 - May 2015 (6 months) Indiana

Education

Indiana University-Northwest
Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2010 - 2014)